<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<MedicineDetails>
  <Medicine>
    <Details>
      Imitrex (sumatriptan) is a headache medicine that narrows blood vessels around the brain. Sumatriptan also reduces substances in the body that can trigger headache pain, nausea, sensitivity to light and sound, and other migraine symptoms.
      Imitrex is available as oral tablets, a nasal spray, and as an injection. It used to treat migraine headaches in adults. Imitrex will only treat a headache. It will not prevent headaches or reduce the number of attacks.
      Imitrex should not be used to treat a common tension headache or a headache that causes loss of movement on one side of your body. Use this medicine only if your condition has been confirmed by a doctor as migraine headaches.
    </Details>
    <InfoHeader>
      Important information
    </InfoHeader>
    <Info>
      You should not use Imitrex if you have uncontrolled high blood pressure, heart problems, certain heart rhythm disorders, a history of heart attack or stroke, or circulation problems that cause a lack of blood supply within the body.
      Do not use this medicine if you have used an MAO inhibitor in the past 14 days, such as isocarboxazid, linezolid, methylene blue injection, phenelzine, rasagiline, selegiline, or tranylcypromine.
      Also tell your doctor if you are taking an antidepressant such as citalopram (Celexa), desvenlafaxine (Pristiq), duloxetine (Cymbalta), escitalopram (Lexapro), fluoxetine (Prozac, Sarafem), fluvoxamine (Luvox), paroxetine (Paxil), sertraline (Zoloft), or venlafaxine (Effexor).
      Imitrex will only treat a headache that has already begun. It will not prevent headaches or reduce the number of attacks.
      Do not use Imitrex within 24 hours before or after using any other migraine headache medicine.
    </Info>
    <IntakeInfoHeader>
      How should I take Imitrex?
    </IntakeInfoHeader>
    <IntakeInfo>
      Use Imitrex as soon as you notice headache symptoms. Follow all directions on your prescription label and read all medication guides or instruction sheets. Use the medicine exactly as directed.
      You may receive your first dose in a hospital or clinic setting to quickly treat any serious side effects.
      Read and carefully follow any Instructions for Use provided with your medicine. Ask your doctor or pharmacist if you do not understand these instructions.
      Take a Imitrex tablet whole with a full glass of water. Do not split the tablet.
      After using Imitrex: If your headache does not completely go away, or goes away and comes back, use a second dose if it has been at least 2 hours since your first dose.
      Never use more than your recommended dose. Overuse of migraine headache medicine can make headaches worse. Tell your doctor if the medicine seems to stop working as well in treating your migraine attacks.
      Do not take more than 200 milligrams of oral Imitrex within 24 hours.
      Do not use more than 40 milligrams of Imitrex nasal spray within 24 hours.
      Call your doctor if your symptoms do not improve, or if you have more than 4 headaches in one month (30 days).
    </IntakeInfo>
    <WarningHeader>
      What happens if I miss a dose?
    </WarningHeader>
    <Warning>
      Since Imitrex is used when needed, it does not have a daily dosing schedule. Call your doctor if your symptoms do not improve after using this medicine.
    </Warning>
  </Medicine>
</MedicineDetails>